[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Most of his party thinks he's crackers (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Most", "of", "his", "party", "thinks", "he", "'s", "crackers", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "For once in a while I'm extremely grateful for your British roots.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "once", "in", "a", "while", "I", "'m", "extremely", "grateful", "for", "your", "British", "roots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "What do you really think of Vladimir Putin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "really", "think", "of", "Vladimir", "Putin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Smart", "and", "remarkably", "--", "we", "had", "a", "really", "good", "blunt", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vladimir Putin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "How blunt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "blunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Brutally blunt.", "answer_tokens": ["Brutally", "blunt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What is your take on, on where we are?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", ",", "on", "where", "we", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, first, all the problems are probably being intensified by the economic challenges we face.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "all", "the", "problems", "are", "probably", "being", "intensified", "by", "the", "economic", "challenges", "we", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How much do you trust him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "trust", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think it's an interesting commentary on the world in which we're living that admitting that the holocaust occurred qualified as being a moderate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "interesting", "commentary", "on", "the", "world", "in", "which", "we", "'re", "living", "that", "admitting", "that", "the", "holocaust", "occurred", "qualified", "as", "being", "a", "moderate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "And it's just going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "just", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "No, we don't have to believe it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "believe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What was he like behind close doors away from, you know, that's with the public utterances?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "behind", "close", "doors", "away", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "with", "the", "public", "utterances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Smart", "and", "remarkably", "--", "we", "had", "a", "really", "good", "blunt", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "ORGAN: How blunt?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "blunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Brutally blunt.", "answer_tokens": ["Brutally", "blunt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Did Putin ever renege on a personal agreement he made to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Putin", "ever", "renege", "on", "a", "personal", "agreement", "he", "made", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "No he did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "he", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Putin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "So behind closed doors, he could be trusted?", "question_tokens": ["So", "behind", "closed", "doors", ",", "he", "could", "be", "trusted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "He kept his word and all the deal that we made.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "kept", "his", "word", "and", "all", "the", "deal", "that", "we", "made", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Can you just share with us a little bit about why you think that's so important?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "just", "share", "with", "us", "a", "little", "bit", "about", "why", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "so", "important", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Well, coming to your family as you're talking women in the workforce, who do you think might make the better president, your wife or your daughter?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "coming", "to", "your", "family", "as", "you", "'re", "talking", "women", "in", "the", "workforce", ",", "who", "do", "you", "think", "might", "make", "the", "better", "president", ",", "your", "wife", "or", "your", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "The day after tomorrow, my wife because she's had more experience.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "day", "after", "tomorrow", ",", "my", "wife", "because", "she", "'s", "had", "more", "experience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Can you put as all out of our misery?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "put", "as", "all", "out", "of", "our", "misery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "What is the ways first, you and Newt Gingrich eventually worked it up between you -- how do you get stuff done in this dysfunctional Washington?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "ways", "first", ",", "you", "and", "Newt", "Gingrich", "eventually", "worked", "it", "up", "between", "you", "--", "how", "do", "you", "get", "stuff", "done", "in", "this", "dysfunctional", "Washington", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "We worked it out when he was trying to run me out of town.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "worked", "it", "out", "when", "he", "was", "trying", "to", "run", "me", "out", "of", "town", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1996"]}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Why did they do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "they", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Because consistently, with the single exception of my getting reelected in 1996, the people who agree with us on the gun issue have not been able to protect the people they elect.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "consistently", ",", "with", "the", "single", "exception", "of", "my", "getting", "reelected", "in", "1996", ",", "the", "people", "who", "agree", "with", "us", "on", "the", "gun", "issue", "have", "not", "been", "able", "to", "protect", "the", "people", "they", "elect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Isn't it about political (ph) courage?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "about", "political", "(", "ph", ")", "courage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, it is not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "is", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Does he do a good Bono impression?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "do", "a", "good", "Bono", "impression", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "He does.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "He does?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "He does.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Now, first of all, what was your reaction when you heard Bono pretending to be you?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "Bono", "pretending", "to", "be", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "It was pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VB", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "What is the point of this film?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "point", "of", "this", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I think the point of the film is really to first of all, to really listen and see -- just to see what are these brilliant minds thinking.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "point", "of", "the", "film", "is", "really", "to", "first", "of", "all", ",", "to", "really", "listen", "and", "see", "--", "just", "to", "see", "what", "are", "these", "brilliant", "minds", "thinking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Sharon, would the world be a less dangerous, less warmongering place if more women run countries?", "question_tokens": ["Sharon", ",", "would", "the", "world", "be", "a", "less", "dangerous", ",", "less", "warmongering", "place", "if", "more", "women", "run", "countries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "You know, what I think that maybe in a better question for you to answer as a man.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "what", "I", "think", "that", "maybe", "in", "a", "better", "question", "for", "you", "to", "answer", "as", "a", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Is that still unfair?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "still", "unfair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, for me, it's -- has a little bit of the difference between erotica and pornography.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "has", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "the", "difference", "between", "erotica", "and", "pornography", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "And was Miley into that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "was", "Miley", "into", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, I'm not so much expressing an opinion here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "so", "much", "expressing", "an", "opinion", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What do you think, Sharon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Sharon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "TONE: You know, I think that when we're looking at a pop and rock entertainment, and someone who's pop and rock entertainer, there's a question of this -- of entertainment.", "answer_tokens": ["TONE", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "when", "we", "'re", "looking", "at", "a", "pop", "and", "rock", "entertainment", ",", "and", "someone", "who", "'s", "pop", "and", "rock", "entertainer", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "question", "of", "this", "--", "of", "entertainment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}}]